covestor.com 2010-05-24

# Privacy Policy - Covestor

## Last Updated: 20 June 2008

## Introduction

At Covestor our most important asset is our relationship with you. Therefore, for both you and us, it is essential we safeguard the privacy of the personal information we maintain about you.

Your information is yours and we respect that. This policy outlines the types of information Covestor collects about you and how that information is used. The policy applies to all current and former Members of Covestor.

Covestor is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.covestor.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Blain Reinkensmeyer using the Contact Us form. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

## What Information we collect and how we use it 

### Registration Information

When you sign up to become a member of Covestor we collect personal information from you if you choose to disclose. This information includes your name, state, country, age, education, professional information, and your email address. You may also choose to supply profile description as well as a link to your own website and a photograph. Once you register with Covestor and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. We use the Registration Information to open an account with us, to provide services that may be tailored to your jurisdiction and to contact you. We do not use the registration information to identify you on the site unless you have chosen to share your identity.

### Activity Information

Having become a Covestor member we collect and maintain information about your membership activity. This activity includes your trading ideas, executed transactions, positions, history, comments, subscriptions to other members as well as ratings of other members’ trading ideas and comments and their ratings of you. We publish this information and derivative products of this information on our site and we use this information to provide the services you have requested.

## Invite-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Covestor stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

### Communications from the Site

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

## Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

### Verification Information

As an active Covestor member you may give us information to access your trading records from your Broker. This Verification Information is only used by our security partners to verify the Activity Information within strict security parameters and is not accessible anywhere on our site and not maintained on our servers. See our security policy for more details. 

### Web Site Usage

When you visit our website, we use “cookies” or other similar Web tools to enhance the user experience. These tools enable us to recognize you when you return to our site, and to maintain your Web session while you browse throughout the site, as well as helping us provide you with a better, more personalized experience. Our cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information.

Some of our business partners (e.g., tracking utility company) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.covestor.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

Covestor automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Covestor cookie information and the pages you request. We use this information to improve the functionality and usability of our services. Our log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Covestor. Please be aware that we, Covestor, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

## Amending Your Account Information

### Accuracy of Information

We are committed to keeping accurate and up-to-date records to help ensure the integrity of the services we offer. If you identify an inaccuracy, or need to make a change to it, please either update the information if you are able directly on our website (go to your Fact Sheet Editor) or alternatively Contact Us. If you believe any information to be erroneous you can contact Covestor and we will endeavor to verify and correct it if erroneous. You may not change any information for other people put on the system, including comments they make about you or your information.

### You can terminate your membership and remove all your Information at any time

You may terminate your Covestor membership at any time by contacting us directly. You can request your Registration, Activity and Verification information be removed from our systems, and our security partners systems, and all data will be removed subject to any legal requirements to keep it. Comments added to other members’ blog posts may remain but will no longer be attributable to you. Information may remain anonymously within aggregated data sets, and portions may remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted if there is a legal requirement, as well as on third party systems we do not directly control.

### Covestor can edit information

Covestor has the right to edit, remove or add any information at any time at its sole discretion.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### We do not reveal any Personally Identifiable information

We will not publish any personally identifiable information (e.g. name, email address or contact information) on our site for other to view, unless you choose to publish it yourself on the site (e.g. within your screen name, profile description, comments etc.).

### We do not reveal any Verification information

We do not maintain any verification information on our servers nor publish any Verification Information anywhere. We use it only with our contracted security partners (service providers) who maintain it in an audited secure environment. This is used solely in order to retrieve your trading data and is kept in strict accordance with both our agreed terms and conditions and our security policy.

### You choose what information to make public

You may choose to what personal information is to be published on the Covestor website. Members will be able to search for, access and review this information. Unless you elect to create a Public Fact Sheet this information will only be accessible by other registered members of Covestor.

Should you elect to create a Public Fact Sheet, summary information including recent Activity Information will be made available to non-members and accessible by search engine technologies.

If you use our blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in this forum.

From time to time we post testimonials. We receive permission to post testimonials that may include personally identifiable information prior to posting. In addition, we receive permission to post personally identifiable information within the “Weekly Member Interview” prior to posting. If you would like your testimonial removed, please Contact Us immediately.

### We do not rent or share any Personally Identifiable information except as described in this privacy policy

Covestor does not rent or share any Personal ID Information with third parties that are not our agents or service providers except as described in this privacy policy or otherwise with your permission.

### We may have to provide your information if legally required to do so

Covestor may be required to provide your information under the following circumstances. In response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against actual or threatened legal claims. In addition when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or activities which we believe give rise to legal liability to us or third parties, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Covestor’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law;

### We will notify you of any changes to this policy

Covestor may update this policy at any time. However, we will notify you of significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to your email address or by placing a prominent notice on this section of our site. In the event, Covestor should be acquired by or merged with another company, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Safeguarding Your Information

We take precautions to ensure the information we collect about you is protected and is accessed only by authorized individuals and organizations. See our security policy for more details.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as investment portfolio on our site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can Contact Us.

E-mail: [support@covestor.com](mailto:support@covestor.com)
